栗宝 又到了玩游戏的时间啦
Okay, Chestnut, it's time to play that game
我们边喝酒边交账单的游戏
where we take shots while we pay our bills
麦克斯神来之笔的取名为
That Max so cleverly named,
"我们边喝酒边交账单的游戏"
"That game where we take shots while we pay our bills."
如果你想姐取个更好的名字
Hey, if you want me to think of a better name,
那我们就该停止在付账单时喝酒
we should probably stop taking shots while we pay our bills.
如果这账单是首次警告信
If this bill says first warning,
我们就喝一杯 另赏栗宝一根胡萝卜
we take a shot, and Chestnut gets a carrot.
如果是最终警告
If it's a final notice,
就赏栗宝两根胡萝卜 我们喝双份酒
Chestnut gets two carrots, and we take a double shot.
如果是已转交到收债公司
And if it's gone into collections,
我们就"饮弹"自尽 并赏栗宝三根胡萝卜
we shoot ourselves, and Chestnut gets three carrots.
另外 姐想喝的时候就要喝
And also, I'm gonna take shots whenever I want to.
好啦 只剩几张账单
All right, only a couple bills to go
但我们口袋也只剩149块钱
and $149 to pay them.
149是单数 喝
That's an odd number. Shots!
我们的电费是72块
Man, our electric bill is $72.
72是双数 喝
That's an even number. Shots!
接下来 我有煤气[屁]
Next up, I have gas.
多谢你这次事先警告啊
Ah, thanks for the heads-up this time.
我们还剩77块 而账单是76.84块
We have $77, and the bill's only $76.84.
是数字 喝
Numbers! Shots!
这是我们第一次收支打平
This is the first time we've ever broken even.
等等 我们收支平衡时 该干嘛啊
Wait, what do we do when we break even?
喝酒吗
Shots?
缴清账单 神清气爽
I'm so proud we paid all our bills
真钱付款 我最骄傲
and with actual American dollars this time.
里面可能有掺杂到点古巴比索
There might've been a couple of pesos in the mix,
不然就是那个硬币有只新驴子
that or the nickel has a sweet new donkey.
姑娘们快看 我买了新iPhone
Look, girls, I got the new iPhone,
Siri觉得我超幽默呢
and Siri thinks I'm hilarious.
听说那台手机镜头很适合自拍
I hear that phone has a great camera for selfies
而你的应该是 矮人自拍
or, in your case, elfies.
麦克斯 笑一个
Smile, Max.
漂亮 微话题"孤独终老"
Nice. #willdiealone.
哇 已经有人点赞了
Oh, already got a like.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
大消息宣布
Big news.
我终于遇到了我"来自梦里的他"
I finally met the man of my dreams.
苏菲 这哪算新闻 咱俩都认识几年了
Sophie, that's not news. You've known me for years.
厄尔 或许在不同地点
Oh, Earl, another place,
不同时间 不同女人
another time, another woman,
不同男人的情况下吧
another man.
姑娘们 来清理下我的卡座吧
Hey, girls, you better wipe down my booth.
我男朋友在停他的林肯轿车
My boyfriend's parking his Lincoln outside.
他先放我下车 一方面是绅士
Yeah, he dropped me off first 'cause he's a class act
一方面是为了要穿上裤子
and 'cause he had to put his pants back on.
你在这儿啊 我的小可爱[花生]
There she is. There's my peanut.
你们听到没 他叫我"小可爱"
You hear that? He calls me his peanut.
我勒个去
Holy crap,
才分别一会 她又更漂亮了
she's looking even prettier than the last time I saw her.
你做了什么
What'd you do,
下车走到餐厅的路上你抹了"美颜霜"吗
get some beauty creams on the way from the car to the diner?
可能是哦
Oh, maybe.
苏菲 很高兴看到你爱得爽歪歪的
Sophie, it's nice to see you so giddy about something.
你的样子就跟我
Yeah, you're like me sitting on
坐在洗衣店爆震的机器上时一样爽
that broken washer at the laundromat.
我叫尼奇 但我的朋友叫我...
I'm Nicky, but my friends call me
时都是为了借钱
when they need money.
我叫卡洛琳 她叫麦克斯
I'm Caroline. This is Max.
我每次看到你这个年纪的男人
I'm gonna ask you the same question
我都会问同个问题
I ask every guy around your age.
你是我亲爹吗
Are you my dad?
能请其中一位美女
Maybe one of you dolls can get me
帮忙倒杯水 我好吞下抗胃酸钙片吗
a glass of water to wash down my tums?
他又性感又有胃溃疡
Sexy and he has an ulcer.
行 我顺便去给你们拿菜单跟酒单
Sure, I'll go get you some menus and the wine list.
不用太开心
Don't get excited.
单子上只有
That's just a list of everything
卡洛琳去年唧歪[酒]过的事情而已
Caroline's whined about in the last year.
那位罗伯特·得脑弱是什么来路
What's up with Robert De Zero over there?
我以前也有过那样的皮衣
I used to have a leather jacket like that.
但我发现 男子汉大丈夫 能露手臂
Then I realized, when you have the right to bear arms,
就必须露之 宝贝
you bare them, baby.
煎蛋 上菜
Omelet. Pick up.
奥列格是在嫉妒吧
I think Oleg just got jealous.
奥列格还掉了不少腋毛屑在蛋上
I think Oleg just got underarm dandruff in these eggs.
请享用
Enjoy.
这是你们的菜单
Here are your menus,
菜单上有配图的从1974年开始就没货
and we're out of everything in the pictures since 1974.
图上笑着吃松饼的小姑娘
So the little girl smiling eating a waffle,
已经当上奶奶 宾州车站就是她的家
she's a grandma now, and she calls Penn Station home.
美女们拿去 麻烦你们了
Here you go, dolls, for your trouble.
一百块 这就像天上掉钱一样
100 bucks? It's like free money.
如果给他的是干净的杯子
Can you imagine what he would've given us
他会给多少小费啊
if the glasses were clean?
啥事都没做就赚到这么多钱
All this money and I didn't even do anything.
我再加撇小胡子就能当卡戴珊了
I'm one mustache away from being a Kardashian.
尼奇是大牌私人庄家
Yeah, Nicky's a big-shot bookie
有一只约克夏
with a yorkie and a membership
还有赛马场的贵宾室会员
to the vip lounge at the race track.
有约克夏还有绿色皮衣
A yorkie and a green leather jacket?
你简直梦幻得不真实
Are you even real?
我超喜欢赛马
I love horse racing.
我以前常去赛马场
I used to go to the track all the time,
不是我显摆 但我有一只纯种马
and not to brag, but I do own a thoroughbred.
她是有一只
Oh, yeah, she does.
我从窗户看过它吃垃圾桶里的东西
I see it eating out of the garbage can from my window.
你看 这是栗宝的照片
Here, that's Chestnut.
长得真美
That's a beauty,
但还是没有我身边的小可爱美
but not as much a beauty as my peanut right here.
他刚才把我跟一匹马比了
Oh, he just compared me to a horse,
可姐还是听得心花怒放
But I like it anyway.
两位美女何不跟着我们
Why don't you two dolls join us
明天下午一起去赛马场的贵宾室
at the track's turf club some afternoon?
我们很忙 而且那里很远...
Oh, we're busy, and it's all the way out in--
-你出钱吗 -当然
- Are you paying? - Of course.
那我们一定去
Oh, then we're there.
我们何不现在就去
In fact, can we go right now?
是啊 我们俩现在也没事
Yeah, we're not doing anything.
麦克斯 你看这马场贵宾俱乐部
Max, look, the turf club.
我们高高在上
Us way up here,
马匹在下面的赛道上
The horses down there on the track
被人强行拉进起跑门栅
being forced into their starting gates.
太让人兴奋了
This is so exciting.
小姐 我们才刚到30秒
Girl, we've been here 30 seconds,
你就已经兴奋地吹号[嗑药]了
and you already blew your bugle.
控制一下好吗
Pace yourself.
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Max, Caroline,
这边
Over here!
我好久没看苏菲这么开心了
Wow, I haven't seen Sophie this happy
上次还是她在我们大楼前
since that girl slipped on the ice
看到有人在冰上滑倒
in front of our building.
那人是我 麦克斯
That girl was me, Max,
那次真的伤到我尾椎了
And I really hurt my coccyx.
你有尾椎 这么酷炫啊 改天约一下啊
You have a coccyx? You want to go out sometime?
姑娘们好
Hey, girls.
小可爱 坐过来一点
Come on, peanut. Get a little closer to me.
靠近点 再靠近点
Closer. Little closer.
靠近 再靠近一点
姑娘们 我能说啥 离她再近都不够
What can I say, girls? I can't get close enough.
你们听到没 他再近都不够
Do you hear that? He can't get close enough.
太感谢你邀请我们来了
Thank you so much for inviting us.
回到赛场的感觉真是太好了
It feels great to be back at the track again.
毕竟赛马可以说是
Ah, horse racing is, after all,
王族的运动
the sport of kings.
我对那里的帝王蟹运动比较感兴趣
I'm more interested in the sport Of king crab legs right over there.
所以这里是吃到饱呢
So is this an all-you-can-eat deal here,
还是吃到被服务员拉走的那种
or will a waiter come drag me away?
爱吃多少吃多少
Knock yourself out.
你这样的姑娘能吃多少呢
How much could a girl like you possibly eat?
你知道眼镜蛇能吞下一整只猪吗
You know how a cobra can swallow an entire pig?
她就像那样
It's like that.
卡洛琳 你想要两只还三只
Hey, Caroline, you want two or three?
麦克斯说你们是
So Max tells me you met
24小时前在24小时健身房碰到的
at 24 Hour Fitness 24 hours ago.
是啊 他在手倒立区发现的我
Yup, he spotted me in a handstand.
尼奇 我该下注哪只
Nicky, who am I gonna bet on?
除了我之外 你喜欢哪个
Who do you like, besides me?
苏菲 赌"裙装混乱"这匹马
Sophie, go with Mess In a Dress.
她早晨的冲力很足
She had great morning sprints,
首次戴赛马眼罩[跑较快]
first-time blinkers,
骑师称重低于标准一磅
Jockey weighed in a pound under,
在另一赛马大赛中
And at The Preakness,
1.7公里长的比赛 她排第二
She was second in seven furlongs,
而这场比赛只有1.2公里长
And this race is only six furlongs.
你说得太长才是真的
Yeah, you're talking for long.
我觉得我要赌三号马
Yeah, I think I'm gonna go with number three,
"我的汉克叔叔"
My Uncle Hank.
我的汉克叔叔
My uncle Hank?
他出狱了吗
He's out of jail?
那我们赶紧吃完就走人吧
Yeah, we should probably eat this and head out.
看 那是我选的马
Oh, see, that's my horse.
我的马 "我的汉克叔叔"
My horse, Uncle Hank.
看 他刚拉屎了
And look, see? He just pooped.
他想装没事逃跑
He's trying to get away from it.
这事我懂 我也是这样的
I know about that. That's how I am.
好了 得去工作赚钱了
Okay, got to make the donuts, but first,
但老妹 先给哥香一口
give me that kisses, sister.
真浪漫
Aw, so romantic.
麦克斯 或许我们也该加入玩一把
Max, maybe we should get in on the action.
不要 他们太"舌来舌往"了
Nah, that's a lot of tongue for me.
我是说下注啦
No, I meant place a bet.
麦克斯 我好像被强制加入"三人行"了
And, Max, I think I'm in a three-way.
你加入"三人行"的样子
Well, you look exactly the way I imagined
跟我想象中的如出一辙 无聊到读书
you'd look in a three-way--reading.
来嘛 我们不是有天上掉下的钱吗
Come on, we have that free money,
而且你明明就爱赌博
and you love to gamble.
但我不赌傻逼东西 只赌不戴套之类的事
Yeah, but nothing stupid, just, like, not using a condom.
算了 管它的
Oh, what the hell?
等等 尼奇 给
Wait, wait, Nicky, Nicky, here.
这钱给你 "裙装混乱"下注200快
Here's your money. 200 on Mess In a Dress.
等等 我觉得我裙中也"混乱"了
Oh, wait, I think I have a mess in my dress.
没问题 美女
You got it, doll,
我会叫人再送点特制酥饼过来
and I'm sending over some of those special popovers.
苏菲 记得吃一个
Sophie, make sure you get one.
你们听到了没
Oh, do you hear that?
其中一个酥饼里面会有戒指
There's gonna be a ring in one of those popovers.
我完全没听到这句
I didn't hear any of that.
如果不是为了藏戒指
Well, why else would someone order popovers
谁会没事点酥饼啊
unless they were gonna hide a ring in it?
我刚才把《海底总动员》的全剧组都吃了
I just ate the entire cast of Finding Nemo.
我不是吃到恶心
I'm not saying I'm sick.
只是胃里的那条小丑鱼很想逃出来
I'm just saying that clown fish wants out.
女士们 下午好 慢慢享用酥饼
Afternoon, ladies. Enjoy the popovers.
你吃完了吗
And are you finished with that?
应该说它们跟我玩完了
Ah, let's just say it's finished with me.
它们出栅了
And they're off.
太刺激了
This is so exciting.
是啊 不知道藏在哪个里
I know. I wonder which one it's in.
好吧 不是这个
Oh. Oh, not that one.
好吧 惨了 也不是这个
All right. Whoops, not that one.
你看 这是我们的马
Look, look, there's our horse,
"裙装混乱"
Mess in a dress.
她领先呢
She's in the lead.
不 也不是这个
Oh, no, not that one.
好耶 好耶 好耶
Yes, yes, yes.
不要 不要 不要
No, no, no.
赢家是"裙装混乱"
And the winner is Mess In a Dress.
我们赢了 赢啦
We won! We won.
我们现在是赢家吗
Are we being winners right now?
我都不知道怎么当个赢家
I don't know how to be that.
我突然都不知道我的手该放哪了
Suddenly I don't know what to do with my hands.
啥都没有
Nothing.
谁会没事点个酥饼
I mean, who in the hell would order popovers
然后里面不藏钻戒啊
and not hide a diamond ring in it?
拿去吧 美女们 六百大洋
Here you go, dolls. 6 big ones.
麦克斯 太棒了
Max, this is incredible.
我们本来有两百 现在有六百
We had 200, and now we have 600.
天上掉下来更多的钱
Even more free money.
服务员 给我的小可爱上一份香蕉圣代
And, waiter, bring my peanut one of those banana splits.
你们听到了吗
You hear that?
在香蕉圣代的最下面
There's a diamond ring
有一只钻石戒指
in the bottom of the banana split.
利昂 你的辛苦费
And, Leon, for your trouble.
真的吗 一百块
Really? 100?
是的 在本宫有钱之前也曾是个女服务员
Yup, I was a waitress before I was rich.
而且在我吃了那鱼之后
And also after that fish,
我可能需要你背我去地铁站
I might need you to carry me to the subway.
正在摸索我裤子的人啊
Whoever that is going through my pants,
老娘可是有枪的人
you should know I have a gun.
麦克斯 是我 卡洛琳
Max, it's me, Caroline.
所以我才买了把枪啊
Why do you think I bought the gun?
麦克斯 你也知道我们就下了一次注
Okay, Max, you know how today we won 600 on our 200
就用200块赢了600块吧
after just that one horse race?
没错 那是很离奇 但远不如
Yeah, that was weird, but not as weird
我睁开眼看见你站在黑暗中
as waking up to see you standing in the dark
跟我的裤子"上三垒"这么离奇
going to third base with my pants.
如果我明天用今天赢来的钱去下注
If I bet our winnings with the three-to-one odds
赔率一赔三的马
on this horse tomorrow,
你知道我能让咱们赚多少钱吗
Do you know how much I can make us?
我想想 2进位到...滚出去
Let's see. 2, carry the 1--Get out.
我这有一份赛马快报
I have the racing form right back here.
那玩意碰过你的股沟 别拿上我的床
Don't bring that over here. That's been in your crack.
瞧 这里
See? Right here.
明天第一场比赛 "喷气飞鲸"
First race tomorrow-- There She Blows.
如果她这么早就起来吹箫[喷气]
If she's blowing that early in the morning,
那这钱也算花得值了
she deserves our money.
我做足了研究
I've done all the research
还跟栗宝确认过了
and checked it with Chestnut.
我有十足的把握 就像明天太阳一定会升起
It's a sure thing, like the sun coming up tomorrow
或是那个索马里海盗
Or that Somali pirate
很难再有机会接戏一样
never getting another acting job again.
你说染赌瘾就染 还光明正大
You go out and get addicted to horse racing
而老娘费尽心思 才敢公开我嗑药抽麻
after I worked so hard to put pills and weed on the table?
我才没有染赌瘾
I am not addicted.
快说你的钱在哪里
Now, where's your cash?
我知道钱不在小猪扑满里
'cause it wasn't in your piggy bank,
因为某个不是我的人 把它打碎了
which someone-- not me--broke.
还觉得自己没染赌瘾吗
You think you don't have a problem?
那好 你可以把钱拿走
Then, fine, you can have the money.
你不会后悔的 钱在哪里
You won't be sorry. Where is it?
在我的咪咪罩里
In my bra.
那你的咪咪罩在哪
Where's your bra?
罩在我的咪咪外
On my boobs.
你居然穿着咪咪罩睡觉
You sleep in your bra?
没办法
Have to.
上次我晚上把咪咪放出来
Last time I let them out at night,
结果她们到凌晨4点才回来
they didn't come home till 4 A.M.
而且还记不得自己去过哪
and couldn't tell me where they'd been.
麦克斯 麻烦把钱拿出来
Max, just take it out of there, please.
不要 我要说出我跟每一个
Nope, I'll tell you what I tell every guy
想伸手进去的男人说过的
who wants to get in there.
"成人票12块 敬老票10块半"
It's 12 bucks for adults and 10.50 for seniors.
好吧 我可为了咱俩才这样做
Fine, I'm doing this for both of us.
还觉得自己没深陷赌海吗
Still think you don't have a problem?
妈的 在哪儿呢
Geez, where is it?
没有地图或导游吗
Is there a map or a tour guide?
就在你的左前方 大概还有20分钟的路程
Coming up on your left. You're about 20 minutes away.
"山峰"比较高 或许你该坐缆车
It's quite a walk. You might want to take the tram.
找到了
Got it.
自我感觉还良好吗
Feel good about yourself?
明天比赛后就会很好了
I will after that race tomorrow.
我保证 不会再有要"伸手"的情况
And I promise I'll never do that again.
我汉克叔叔也是这么说的
That's what my Uncle Hank said.
我是说绝不会再伸手跟你要钱啦
No, I meant I'll never ask you for money again.
汉克叔叔的老婆也是这么说的
That's what Uncle Hank's wife said.
绝不再赌钱
No more gambling.
你是不是看过他的案件资料 每句话都学他
Now I feel like you read the transcript of Uncle Hank's case.
等下 里面还有呢
Oh, wait, you forgot some.
逗你玩的 太晚上被人抓挺爽的
Just kidding, it's late, and it felt kind of good.
麦克斯 希望卡洛琳能快点来上班
Max, I hope Caroline gets here soon,
因为要是她上班迟到了整整四个小时
'cause if that girl walks in one full hour late,
我会忍不住对她跪地膜拜
I'll have to respect the hell out of her.
她还在赛马场
She's still at the track,
我超级想知道我们那匹马赢了没有
and I'm dying to know how our horse did.
这种心悬在半空的感觉
So much suspense.
让我想在验孕棒上尿尿来应景一下
I feel like I should be peeing on a stick.
你们俩还在赌马啊
You girls are still playing the horses.
注意适可而止
Keep that in check.
当初我的赌瘾愈演愈烈
My gambling problem got so bad
最后都没钱应付我的毒瘾了
I couldn't even afford my drug problem.
你回来啦 情况如何
You're back! So how did we do?
旗开得胜
We did great.
我们下注"喷气飞鲸"赢了
We won our bet on There She Blows.
太棒了 赢了多少
Yes! How much did we get?
有赢到加得起牛油果那么多吗
Are we talking "add avocado" money?
一开头旗开得胜 接着不温不火
Well, we did do great, and then we did not great.
然后情况急转直下 之后一落千丈
And then we did bad, and then we did real bad.
最后一败涂地
And then we did terrible.
长话短说 我的抗胃酸钙片吃完了
Long story short, I'm out of tums,
还有 我们欠尼奇3千块
and we owe Nicky $3,000.
是你 你欠尼奇3千块
You--you owe Nicky.
当初我沉迷于吃披萨味的品客薯片时
When I got addicted to pizza Pringles,
我可没赖你 让你遭罪哦
I didn't make it your problem.
你的口臭让大家都跟着遭罪
Your breath made it all our problems.
麦克斯 尼奇不是什么危险人物吧
Max, Nicky's not, like, dangerous, is he?
应该不是 就算他是
I bet he's not, but even if he is,
也不用担心
don't worry.
你可以轻松在林肯车的后备箱里
You can survive in the trunk of Lincoln
被关五六天不死 绝对没问题
for five, six days easy.
麦克斯 我可以把所有钱都赢回来
Max, I know I can make all of this money back
只要再赢一把就行
if I just win one more race.
只需赌一把有十足把握的
I just need a sure thing.
根本没有什么事能有十足把握
There is no such thing as a sure thing,
除了我妈从不来学校接我 这我有十足的把握
except my mother never picking me up from school.
明天有两匹马 看起来赢面很大
Look, there are two horses tomorrow that look really good,
"削他先生"和"盖里街的小房子"
Buck That and Little House on The Gary.
"盖里街的小房子" 那是我朋友艾迪的马
Little House on The Gary -- that's my friend Eddie's horse.
我们没空陪你玩
We don't have time to pretend
你有一个朋友叫艾迪的游戏
you have a friend named Eddie right now.
是真的 艾迪·琼斯
I do. Eddie jones.
他是个有名的骑师 我们在裁缝店认识的
He's a famous jockey. We met at the tailor.
我们在裁裤腿的时候聊了起来
We got to talking as we were both having our jeans hemmed.
你在哪里买的牛仔裤 杰西潘小尼百货吗
Where'd you buy them, J.C.Puny?
阿憨 拜托 你一定要帮我
Han, please, you have to help me.
去跟你的朋友艾迪聊聊
You have to talk to your friend Eddie
帮我搞到明天比赛的消息
and get me the scoop on the race tomorrow.
好吧 但有一个条件
Okay, I'll help on one condition:
不许麦克斯再嘲笑我矮
No more short jokes from Max.
她可以的
She can do that.
你可以的对吧 麦克斯 不要回答
You can do that, right, Max? Don't answer.
所以从现在开始 不许再说嘲笑矮子的...
So no more short jokes starting right--
好吧 但首先
Okay, wait, but first,
我是不是在婴儿食品罐上见过你啊
didn't I see you on a baby food jar?
老鼠弄了个小小捕鼠器来抓你
A mouse set a trap for you.
你个霍比特人 不是要把魔戒送到魔多吗
And don't you have to bring a ring to Mordor?
好了 可以了
Okay, let's do this.
艾迪说让我们来下面找他
Eddie said he'd meet us down here.
阿憨 真是太感谢你了
Han, I really appreciate this.
你真是帮了我一个很大很大的忙
You're doing me such a big, big favor.
我们都很意外 你能做任何跟"大"有关的事
Yeah, and we're surprised you can do anything big.
我受够了
Okay, that's it.
阿憨 别走啊
Han, wait.
老子不干了
I don't need it!
麦克斯 瞧你做的好事
Max, see what you did?
怎么了 我现在是自动模式
What? I was on autopilot.
我刚说什么了
What did I say?
阿憨 麦克斯保证不会再犯了
Han, please, Max won't say anything.
很好 因为我的容忍是有限度的
Good, 'cause I've had it up to here.
个子小所以肚量也小吗
You don't have it up to there.
老子不干了
Don't need it!
麦克斯
Max!
求你不要再开这种玩笑了
Please, you have to stop with the short jokes.
这可事关我的人生
This is my life.
但吐槽不倦就是我的人生
But that's my life.
那你继续 很快我就会被扔进东河底
Keep it up, and I'm gonna be at the bottom of the East River
跟你从布鲁克林大桥推下去的
with that hipster artisan cheese truck
那辆嬉皮士手工奶酪车双宿双栖
you pushed off the Brooklyn bridge.
你说得对 我不会再开那种玩笑了
You're right. No more short jokes.
要不我还是在外面等吧
Maybe I should wait outside.
阿憨 艾迪在哪里
So, Han, where's Eddie?
我们得在麦克斯憋昏前
I think we should talk to him as quickly as possible
尽快跟他把话说完
before Max passes out.
我没看见他 但等的时间应该会很"短"
I don't see him. I'm sure he'll be here shortly.
我都憋到内伤了
And I just bit the inside of my mouth.
阿憨
Hey, it's Han!
自从上次简"短"的旅程后 就再没见过面了
I haven't seen you since we took our little trip.
哪有 上次我主办的"小"店主垒球赛
No, man, I saw you after my small business
结束后我还见过你
owners softball game.
对了 我买了辆新车 "迷你"库柏哦
Hey, I got new car, a Mini Cooper.
这就是地狱 老娘身在地狱
This is hell. I'm in hell.
你好 艾迪
Eddie, hi,
你能跟我说说今天的比赛吗
is there anything you can tell me about today's race?
有没有稳赢的
Is there a sure thing?
你最近赌运不佳吗
Oh, you get yourself a bad bet?
何止不佳 简直糟透了
Bad bet and beyond.
跟你说个"小"贴士
Well, let me give you a little tip.
我在外面等你
I'll be outside.
最后冲刺
And coming down the home stretch,
"盖里街的小屋子"暂时领先
Little House on The Gary has the lead.
加油 "盖里街的小屋子"
Come on, Little House on The Gary!
快跑 就像卡洛琳在日落后
Run! Run like Caroline after sundown
经过外国人社区那样狂奔
in an ethnic neighborhood.
马儿马儿 快快跑
The hoof, the hoof, the hoof is on fire!
要赢了 要赢了
He's winning. He's winning.
要赢了
He's winning!
天啊 怎么回事
Oh, no, what's happening?
他落后了
He's falling behind.
上帝啊 我最最亲爱的上帝
Oh, lord. Oh, my sweet, sweet lord.
要输了 要输了
He's losing. He's losing.
要输了
He's losing.
阿憨 你怎么解释
Han, what is happening?
或许我该走了
Well, maybe I'll take off.
你朋友说过有十足的把握
Your friend said it was a sure thing.
都说不存在什么十足的把握
There is no sure thing
除了泰勒·斯威夫特一定会再写分手歌
except another Taylor Swift breakup song.
"盖里街的小屋子"
And Little House on The Gary
摔个狗啃泥 而本次冠军正是"狗啃泥"
falls to pieces as Falls to Pieces wins.
如果我们的马最后跑完
So what do we win if our horse finishes last
还硬着个大鸡鸡闲晃 我们能赢啥
and wanders around the track with a giant erection?
费了半天劲 居然输了
All that and we lost?
谢谢你的午餐
Thanks for lunch.
阿憨 你小到可以把迷你糖果盒当房子
Han, you're so small your house is a Tic Tac box.
你小到可以坐进你车的杯架里
You're so small you ride in your car cupholder.
你小到让人怀疑
You're so small your parents
你的父母是瓢虫和小炸土豆块
are a ladybug and a tater tot.
眉宇之间还真看得出来
I could see that, actually.
老子不干了
I don't need it!
瞧 卡洛琳
You see, Caroline?
所以我才退出赌坛
This is why I quit gambling,
因为理智和自动扶梯总是会崩溃
This and the escalator was always broken.
好啦 消消气
All right, let's just calm down.
这里是赛马场 不是黑帮电影《好家伙》
This is the turf club, not Goodfellas,
虽然这是根据真人真事改编
Though that was placed on real-life events
而且就发生在离这不远的地方
And took place not that far from here.
好吧 或许他不会对我们这么狠
Right, and maybe he won't be so hard on us.
尼奇是苏菲的男朋友
Nicky is Sophie's boyfriend.
我刚和尼奇分手了
Well, I just broke up with Nicky.
为什么
Why?
我看见他把一个欠他钱的人打个半死
I just saw him beat the crap out of some guy that owed him money.
完了 他来了
Oh, no, here he comes.
你们好啊 美女
There you are, dolls.
下一个折断的就是我的狗腿
My leg is next.
真倒霉
Tough break.
我得拿上我3千块走人了
I'm gonna take my 3 grand and go.
小可爱跟我分手了
Peanut just broke up with me,
我要回家
so I'm gonna go home
跟我的狗和我老婆一起上床休息了
and get in bed with my dog and my wife.
我得对你坦白 我们没钱还你
I have to come clean. We don't have your money.
后来我失手了
I got out of control.
美女 别紧张 我是个讲理的人
Doll, relax. I'm a reasonable man.
我们可以商量的嘛
We can work out something.
那就好
Oh, good.
希望他先开枪打死我
Hope he shoots me first.
我宁愿死 也不想听你求他
I'd rather be dead than hear you beg.
你的纯种马还在吗
Still got that thoroughbred?
我明天过来把它带走
I'll come by tomorrow to get it.
他不能夺走我的马
He can't take my horse.
我该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
你可以搬去纽约 改名叫麦克斯
You can always move to New York and change your name to Max.
等等 我已经这么做了
Wait, I already did that.
我真是脑子被马踢了
What is wrong with me?
我早该明白
I should have known better.
我爸就是因为钱进监狱
My father has problems with money.
我肯定有遗传他
It's in my DNA.
现在因为这一次愚蠢的赌马
And now all because of a stupid bet,
我要失去栗宝了
I'm gonna lose Chestnut.
如果能让你感觉好过点
If it makes you feel any better,
我妈有次打赌 还把我输了呢
my mom once lost me in a bet.
她居然认为罗伯特·雷德福有演《窈窕淑男》
Still can't believe she thought Robert Redford was in Tootsie.
我们不能失去栗宝
We can't lose Chestnut.
我靠 我靠 都怪你个笨蛋
Damn it, damn it, damn it, people.
害我得再出江湖
Make me come out of retirement
帮你们擦赌输的屁股
just save your gambling asses.
我只需要100块
Now, all I need is 100 bucks.
卡洛琳 你怀孕到生孩子要多久
Hey, Caroline, how fast can you have a baby?
你好 利昂
Hey. Hi, Leon.
还记得我们吗 给了你100块小费那俩
Remember us, the ones who tipped you 100 bucks?
当然记得 在这里
Oh, of course, it's hard to find
很少有出手这么大方的人
that kind of generosity in this place.
顿时让我再次心怀希望
It gives you hope again.
不好意思 你得把钱还给我们
Yeah, we're gonna need that back.
老实说 我需要这钱
Well, actually, I need all my money.
我上有高堂啊
I support my mother.
改天再好好孝顺吧
Yeah, maybe not today.
麦克斯 我真不敢相信
Max, I can't believe it.
我不但害了自己 还害了我骑的那匹马
I screwed me and the horse I rode in on.
你何不"骑"着它拍部电影 把钱都赚回来
Why don't you film that and get your money back?
卡洛琳 瞧
Caroline, look.
厄尔 你做到了
Earl, you did it.
你救了栗宝
You saved Chestnut.
是啊 我俩都是棕色种马
Yeah, well, we brown studs
当然要互相支持
have to stick together.
这钱我来收
And I'll take that.
因为我也不相信我自己
And since I don't trust myself,
所以我要把这200块捐给我最爱的慈善机构
I'm donating this 200 to my favorite charity,
给
So here.
不许再赌了
Now, no more betting,
人生中唯一有十足把握的就是人必有一死
'cause the only sure thing in life is death.
祝你们愉快
Have a nice day.
一张给你 一张给我
One for you, and one for me.
200块 又回到了天刚掉钱那会
200, we're back to our free money,
这一次要立马把钱存起来
And this time, it's going right in the savings account.
那家银行"利息"不"大"
Well, it's not earning much interest in there.
存这里
Here.
这家银行有两家"大分行"哦
We're keeping this in a bank with two major branches.